Amy, wait!
(Sheldon:)Getting a turtle meant
a great deal to me, too.
(Raj:)Sure.
(Amy:)Unless something
better comes along.
(Sheldon:)Do you want me
to withdraw my application?
(Amy:)What I want is for us
(Amy:)to be planning our
future together.
(Sheldon:)And in that future,
(Sheldon:)are we on the same planet?
Yeah, because I've seen people
(Sheldon:)make the long-distance
thing work.
We're on the same planet!
Okay!
(Sheldon:)Does that planet have
to be Earth?
(Amy:)Are you asking me to go
to Mars with you?
(Sheldon:)I am.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, if I'm going
to a barren,
(Sheldon:)lifeless environment,
(Sheldon:)where the chances of survival
are slim to none,
(Sheldon:)I want you there with me.
(Sheldon:)Why don't we go back
to the apartment,
(Sheldon:)and fill out your application?